Finding Aid for the The Andrew Nelson Lytle 1988 Addition
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- SERIES II. WRITINGS
  - Writings – Typescript: “Can You Teach Creative Writing.” (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings – Typescript: “A Medley: History and Myth and the Artist” (1 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings – Typescript: “A Medley: History and Myth and the Artist” (2 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings – Typescript: “A Medley: History and Myth and the Artist” (3 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings – Typescript: “A Medley: History and Myth and the Artist” (4 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings – Typescript: “The Plumed Serpent and the White Elephant” (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings – Typescript: “The Unclean Lips” (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings ABOUT LYTLE (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings About Lytle – “About Andrew Lytle” (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings About Lytle – “Andrew Lytle: A Personal Remembrance” (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings About Lytle – Interview with Andrew Lytle by Claude Koch (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Writings About Lytle – “In the Inner Chamber: The Velvet Horn” (Box 3, Folder 1)
- SERIES IV. FAMILY (Box 3)
  - Family (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - SERIES V. FINANCIAL (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Financial (Box 3, Folder 1)